http://www.fighthype.com/privacypolicy.html

BERNARD HOPKINS: "RICH KIDS DON'T FIGHT...THEY DON'T HAVE TO, THEY SHOULDN'T, AND THEY NEVER WILL"FLOYD MAYWEATHER KILLS RUMORS OF 2014 PACQUIAO CLASH; EXPOSES SHADY BUSINESS DEALSVIRGIL HUNTER SAYS MAYWEATHER VS. KHAN BECAUSE "MANNY GOT PUT TO SLEEP; AMIR FINISHES ON HIS FEET"FLOYD MAYWEATHER SAYS HE'S NOT A TRUE WELTERWEIGHT, BUT DOES HE THINK HE CAN STILL FIGHT AT 140?MICKEY AND CORTEZ BEY SHARE WITH FLOYD MAYWEATHER WHAT IT MEANS TO FIGHT FOR HIMMICKEY BEY TALKS FUTURE PLANS; EYES EVENTUAL SHOWDOWN WITH OMAR FIGUEROAFLOYD MAYWEATHER PLANNING A "DYNAMITE" UNDERCARD WITH TMT FIGHTERS ON MAY 3
Tweet
BACK TO FRONT PAGE
PRIVACY POLICY
Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note: The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
Collection of Information
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.
Advertising
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web
site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name,
address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other
Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of
interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to
know your choices about not having this information used by these companies,
click here.
Cookie/Tracking Technology
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.
Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
Distribution of Information
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.
Commitment to Data Security
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.
Privacy Contact Information
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
By email: privacy@fighthype.com
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
Tweet
BACK TO FRONT PAGE
JANUARY 07, 2014KENNY FLORIAN: "IT WAS A GREAT YEAR TO GET MORE EXPOSURE FOR THE UFC...THIS YEAR, IT'S GOING TO BE FUN"JESSE HART ON DERRICK FINDLEY CLASH: "I WANT HIM TO WANT TO QUIT...I WANT TO EXECUTE"PACQUIAO LAWYER, FRANKLIN GACAL, BLAMES MICHAEL KONCZ FOR TAX ISSUES AND HIDING CONTRACTS; URGES PACQUIAO TO LEAVEJANUARY 06, 2014CANELO ALVAREZ SAYS ALFREDO ANGULO IS NEXT FOR MARCH 8 RETURNJESSE HART RIPS CARL FROCH: "HE'S SATISFIED WITH BARELY GETTING WINS...A C-CLASS FIGHTER"OBSERVE AND FIGHT: 2014 IS OFF AND RUNNING WITH NO SIGNS OF SLOWING DOWNJESSE HART BLASTS BADOU JACK: "I WOULD STOP THAT KID...YOUR CAREER IS A JOKE TO ME"JANUARY 05, 2014SOURCE SAYS BRADLEY IS PACQUIAO'S CHOICE THANKS TO MARQUEZ "DIVA WAYS" AND "MAYWEATHER FACTOR"JANUARY 04, 2014[VIDEO] BERNARD HOPKINS: "RICH KIDS DON'T FIGHT...THEY DON'T HAVE TO, THEY SHOULDN'T, AND THEY NEVER WILL"BOXING GETS LUXURIOUS AS "MONEY" MAYWEATHER HITS THE COVER OF THE DUPONT REGISTRYJANUARY 03, 2014FLOYD MAYWEATHER DISPUTES THAT AMIR KHAN HAS SIGNED A FIGHT CONTRACT; 7 QUESTIONS HE WANTS ANSWERS TOANDRE WARD: "FROCH HAS TWO OPTIONS...MY MOTIVATION IS NOT TO BEAT HIM, BUT TO STOP HIM"JANUARY 02, 2014NAAZIM RICHARDSON BELIEVES ADRIEN BRONER RECEIVING MAYWEATHER BACKLASH AFTER FIRST DEFEATBERMANE STIVERNE ON A MISSION TO BECOME 1ST HAITIAN-BORN HEAVYWEIGHT CHAMPIONFLOYD MAYWEATHER KILLS RUMORS OF 2014 PACQUIAO CLASH; SHADY BUSINESS DEALS EXPOSEDAL BERNSTEIN NOT OPTIMISTIC ABOUT ADRIEN BRONER'S CHANCES AT 147 OR 140: "HE NEEDS TO GET HIMSELF BACK DOWN TO 135"DARNELL BOONE: THE BEST RESUME IN BOXING?JANUARY 01, 2014AL BERNSTEIN TABS KEITH THURMAN AS A FUTURE OPPONENT FOR FLOYD MAYWEATHERJULIAN WILLIAMS: "I DID BETTER THAN A LOT OF OTHER PROSPECTS...I'M REALLY LOOKING FORWARD TO 2014"PAUL DALEY: "I'M A LOT MORE COMPOSED AND CONFIDENT I CAN BEAT ANYONE"DECEMBER 31, 2013AL BERNSTEIN: "2013 WAS A GREAT YEAR FOR THE SPORT"DAQUAN ARNETT ON EDDIE GOMEZ CLASH: "HE DOES A LOT OF GOOD THINGS, BUT NOTHING SPECTACULAR"JERMALL CHARLO: "LIKE THE KLITSCHKOS DID AT HEAVYWEIGHT?ME AND MY BROTHER...WE GONNA TAKE OVER THE DIVISION"DECEMBER 30, 2013TEAM MAIDANA ON FLOYD MAYWEATHER CLASH: "WE HAVE NOT BEEN CONTACTED ABOUT IT...WILL NOT BE BEGGING"AMIR KHAN ON FLOYD MAYWEATHER CLASH: "I'VE SIGNED MY PART...IF HE WANTS TO FACE SOMEONE I'VE BEATEN, SO BE IT"OBSERVE AND FIGHT: 2013 YEAR-END AWARDS - THE PUNCH BOXING WAS LOOKING FORVIRGIL HUNTER SAYS CANELO WILL HAVE A LOT TO PROVE AGAINST MOTIVATED ALFREDO ANGULO: "HE'S ALREADY TRAINING"ZAHIR RAHEEM ON BAYARN JARGAL CLASH: "I WANT TO LEAVE AN IMPRESSION...I WANT TO MAKE A STATEMENT"DECEMBER 29, 2013UFC 168 RESULTS: CHRIS WEIDMAN RETAINS TITLE AFTER ANDERSON SILVA BREAKS LEG IN 2ND ROUNDDECEMBER 28, 2013FIGHTHYPE PREVIEW: UFC 168 WEIDMAN VS. SILVA 2
